Guide to the Duke Real Estate Office records, 1893-2018 and undated UA.10.04.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Real Estate Deeds, 1893-2018; undated
  - File No.: 2107, Grantee: David C. and Lou A. Dellinger, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 March 20 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #7, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2108, Grantee: Ronald & Beverly Perkins, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 September 16 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-12, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 6
  - File No.: 2109, Grantee: Lloyd R. & Judith Fortney, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 September 23 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #23, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2110, Grantee: Robert A. & Ruby Pittillo, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 October 31 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-12, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 6
  - File No.: 2111, Grantee: Harold & Susan Schiffman, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 November 8 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #9, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2112, Grantee: Peter & Joan Marinos, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1974 May 6 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot 4-C, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2113, Grantee: Richard & Georgiana Searles, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 January 23 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot 35, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2114, Grantee: Victor & Lenora Behar, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 April 10 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #4, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2115, Grantee: Charles W. & Lynne Erwin, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1972 February 28 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot 17, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2116, Grantee: John C. & Lessie Detwiler, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 November 10 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 845, Page: 187, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-17, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2117, Grantee: John David & Ruth Ross, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 January 7 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #5, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2118, Grantee: Yihong & Wen-Chi Kong, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 April 8 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #6-B, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2119, Grantee: Hsioh & Lily Wang, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 April 13 (Box 22)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #1, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2120, Grantee: Saul M. & Rachel Schanberg, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 April 24 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #18-F, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 2121, Grantee: Arthur and Florence Lawson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 December 4 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #24, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2122, Grantee: Paul P. & Julia Y. Wang, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1971 January 20 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #10-H, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec.6
  - File No.: 2123, Grantee: John A. and Joan Furlow, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1971 June 1 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2-B, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2124, Grantee: Charles & Peggy Hammond, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1972 April 25 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #6, Blk A, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2125, Grantee: Alvin L. & Karen A. Crumbliss, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1977 December 8 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #5-B, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2126, Grantee: Larry D. and Sue Nelson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1972 May 30 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #5-A, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2127, Grantee: Senol and Bisulay Utku, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1972 August 8 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #13, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2128, Grantee: W. Derek & Priscilla Shows, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1976 August 5 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #3-B, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2129, Grantee: Charles & Patricia Rochmuller, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1976 February 24 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #4-A, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2130, Grantee: John G. & Ellen Lundberg, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1974 July 17 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #3-A, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2131, Grantee: P. Costanzo & S. Roth, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1977 August 19 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #19-E, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2132, Grantee: Franklin & Pamela Cocks, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1974 September 20 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #26, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2133, Grantee: John & Shirley Hanks, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1974 October 1 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #16, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2134, Grantee: Herbert & Marjorie Hacker, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1976 August 6 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2-A, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2135, Grantee: Devendra & Prabha Garg, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1975 February 24 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2-C, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2136, Grantee: Patrick & Sally McKee, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1975 February 18 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #1-C, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8
  - File No.: 2137, Grantee: Arthur & Elizabeth Alt, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1977 April 18 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #15, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 2138, Grantee: Aleksandar & Milena Vesic, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1979 November 26 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 1019, Page: 55-56, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #25, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec.8/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2139, Grantee: Redford & Virginia Williams, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1975 October 1 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 913, Page: 493, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #55, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 2/Paid in full
  - File No.: 2140, Grantee: Clifton & Juanita Kreps, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1980 October 3 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1407 Pettigrew
  - File No.: 2141, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: U. S. Fire Insurance Co., Type: Deed, 1986 May 5 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 1278, Page: 132, Map-Block-Lot: 013-03-004, Comments/Location: 705 Broad Street
  - File No.: 2142, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Bruce Klitzman, Type: Deed, 1988 March 23 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2143, Grantee: Claudia Bloom, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1986 May 23 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #77
  - File No.: 2144, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Nye, Type: Deed, 1984 July 3 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2145, Grantee: Allan Bone, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1986 June 19 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2147, Grantee: Jane Clark Moorman, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1987 February 3 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #35 and 36
  - File No.: 2148, Grantee: Charles Reinhart, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1986 May 27 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2149, Grantee: Roderick & Dianne Broadway, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1988 February 2 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2150, Grantee: Ron W. Djuren, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1988 March 17 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2151, Grantee: Barrie & Jean Hurwitz, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1988 April 21 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2152, Grantee: United States of America, Grantor: Duke, 1988 May 19 (Box 23)
    Comments/Location: Beaufort, NC
  - File No.: 2153, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John A. and Lou M. Blake, Type: Deed, 1988 August 12 (Box 23)
    County: Randolph, Comments/Location: Easement, Historical Monument of Duke U.
  - File No.: 2154, Grantee: Ish and Anu A. Sud, Grantor: Duke, 1988 September 16 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Homesites, Section 9, Lot #38 ('Cornwallis Road)
  - File No.: 2155, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. Richard Tilley, 1984 July 17 (Box 23)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Duke Forest land; Orange Cty.; 15.02 Acres
  - File No.: 2156, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Peter H. & Martha Klopfer, 1986 August 8 (Box 23)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Duke Forest Land
  - File No.: 2156, Grantee: Peter H. and Martha Klopfer, Grantor: Duke, 1986 September 19 (Box 23)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Duke Forest land; Orange Cty.
  - File No.: 2157, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sharon S. Poss, 1988 September 2 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 2406 Pratt St. apartments
  - File No.: 2157, Grantee: Dur. Co. Habitat for Humanity, Grantor: Duke, 1992 November 18 (Box 23)
  - File No.: 2158, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: State of N.C., 1988 January 26 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Lenox Baker/ Erwin Road, Old/New File No.: 467
  - File No.: 2159, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Gary M. and Kathleen Hock, 1988 June 13 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 5.669 acres & 218 Frasier Street
  - File No.: 2160, Grantee: Bernice and Everett Hopkins, Grantor: Duke, 1966 January 10 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1520 Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 2161, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Altmont Corporation, 1990 July 19 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 909-919 & 925-929 Maxwell & 202 Gattis St.
  - File No.: 2162, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: City of Durham, 1990 September 25 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 7.686 Acres E-W Expressway
  - File No.: 2163, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: W. Kimball, Jr. & Mary Griffin, 1990 February 26 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Caswell & Powe Streets
  - File No.: 2164, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Odessa Rigsbee, 1990 April 6 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 306 Alexander Street
  - File No.: 2165, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: R. Taylor Cole, 1991 July 15 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 7 Sylvan Road - Gift Property
  - File No.: 2166, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Marian Scott & James Weaver, 1991 July 11 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 305,307,310,311 Alexander;1711,1713 Pace St.
  - File No.: 2167, Grantee: Thomas & Dawn Naylor, Grantor: Duke, 1977 December 20 (Box 23)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Easement; Orange County
  - File No.: 2168, Grantee: Anna Painter, Grantor: Duke, 1991 September 16 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Lot N.E. Pickett Road & Wade Road
  - File No.: 2169, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Griffin, Pendergraph, etc., 1992 January 24 (Box 23)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1705 Bynum St., Durham
  - File No.: 2170, Grantee: Duke UNIVERSITY, Grantor: Turnpike Properties, Inc., 1989 December 29 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Deed file 2170 A; Dutch Village Inn
  - File No.: 2170, Grantee: Duke Special Ventures, Inc, Grantor: Duke University, 1990 February 22 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Deed file A; re-recorded on the 1989 documents
  - File No.: 2170, Grantee: DAMCO, Grantor: Duke Special Ventures, Inc, 1991 July 1 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Deed file 2170 B
  - File No.: 2170, Grantee: Duke UNIVERSITY, Grantor: DAMCO, 1996 October 30 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Deed file 2170 C
  - File No.: 2171, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Kathryne Brown, 1992 June 11 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 117 S. Buchanan
  - File No.: 2172, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dunbar Realty & Ins. Co., Inc., 1992 August 28 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Lot at corner of Pratt & Fulton Sts.
  - File No.: 2173, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dora Ann Little, 1992 June 18 (Box 24)
    County: Anson, Comments/Location: Anson County, NC; 2-year timber deed
  - File No.: 2173, Grantee: Culp Lumber Company, Grantor: Duke, 1992 July 16 (Box 24)
    County: Anson
  - File No.: 2174, Grantee: Duke & C.D. & Kate Hawkins, Grantor: Kelly W. and Dorothy Carver, 1985 October 4 (Box 24)
    County: Person, Deed Book: 183, Page: 948, Map-Block-Lot: 10/11th to Duke, 1/11th to Hawkins, Comments/Location: Roxboro, Person Co. Hawkins/Duke
  - File No.: 2174.1, Grantee: Duke University, Grantor: Katie Davis Hawkins, Type: deed, 2002 October 15 (Box 24)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2027.
    County: Person, Deed Book: 398, Page: 121, Map-Block-Lot: last 1/11th to Duke, Comments/Location: Roxboro
  - File No.: 2174.2, Grantee: Marvin Painter and Judith Akers, Grantor: Duke, Type: deed, certificate, 2003 January 10 (Box 24)
    County: Person, Deed Book: 410, Page: 278, Map-Block-Lot: 138 Kelly Carver Road, Comments/Location: Roxboro
  - File No.: 2175, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Keenan, Jones, Dixon, etc., 1992 December 16 (Box 24)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: 61.36 Acres; Duke Forest; Orange County
  - File No.: 2176, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Jean Pugh Adams, 1992 December 22 (Box 24)
    County: Mecklen., Comments/Location: 1535 Lovett St., Greensboro - SOLD October 1995
  - File No.: 2177, Grantee: Carteret County, Grantor: Duke, 1993 January 29 (Box 24)
    County: Carteret, Comments/Location: Sea Level Hospital
  - File No.: 2179, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: City of Durham, 1992 February 14 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Street Closing - Pratt St.
  - File No.: 2180, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: City of Durham, 1992 February 14 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Street Closing - Atlas St.
  - File No.: 2182, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Morton & Bernice Lerner, 1993 April 30 (Box 24)
    County: New Han., Comments/Location: Wilmington, NC; New Hanover County
  - File No.: 2183, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Commie & Mellie Riggsbee, 1993 October 7 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 304 Alexander
  - File No.: 2184, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John Henry Pratt, 1993 December 14 (Box 24)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Orange County; .04 Acres
  - File No.: 2185, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: H & A Properties, 1993 November 10 (Box 24)
    County: Chatham, Comments/Location: Easement; Chatham County
  - File No.: 2189, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Susan E. Anderson, 1994 May 18 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 418 Anderson Street
  - File No.: 2190, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Fran Brandon/Jack Wagoner, 1994 June 15 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 3090 Colony Road #E, Durham; SOLD
  - File No.: 2191, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Kreps House Partnership, 1993 December 28 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Pettigrew St.; Center for Documentary Studies
  - File No.: 2192, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: James Hawkins & C.C. Woods, 1993 May 27 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 1851, Page: 576-577, Comments/Location: 3540 Kangaroo Drive
  - File No.: 2193, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Gaston E. Small, 1989 June 6 (Box 24)
    County: Dare, Comments/Location: Lot 163, Carolina Dunes, Dare County
  - File No.: 2194, Grantee: Durham Realty, Inc., Grantor: Durham Public Schools, 1995 May 22 (Box 24)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2020.
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 923 Maxwell Street
  - File No.: 2195, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. J. Kiser, 1994 November 3 (Box 24)
    County: Norfolk, Comments/Location: Norfolk County, MA; SOLD January 1996
  - File No.: 2196, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Ralph Rogers, 1994 December 21 (Box 24)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Orange County
  - File No.: 2197, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Teer, 1990 January 2 (Box 24)
    County: Brunswick, Comments/Location: Brunswick County, Bald Head Island
  - File No.: 2198, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Richard Tinus, 1989 January 4 (Box 24)
    County: Moore, Comments/Location: Moore County; Lots 30 & 33; SOLD both lots
  - File No.: 2199, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Winifred T. Carter, 1995 July 18 (Box 24)
    County: Hancock, Comments/Location: Hancock County, Maine
  - File No.: 2200, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Maidee Boyd, 1989 January 5 (Box 24)
    County: Moore, Comments/Location: Whispering Pines, Pinehurst, NC; SOLD
  - File No.: 2201, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wallace & Sue Vick McCown, 1989 December 27 (Box 24)
    County: Dare, Comments/Location: Lot 195, Dare County; SOLD October 1995
  - File No.: 2202, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Polly P. Hanson, 1995 March 31 (Box 24)
    County: Mecklen., Comments/Location: Charlotte, NC; SOLD December 1995
  - File No.: 2203, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: H. Teer/D.U. Special Ventures, 1988 June 30 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Carolee Apartments
  - File No.: 2204, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Fletcher/D.U. Special Ventures, 1988 June 29 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Jefferson Arms
  - File No.: 2205, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: B. Bunn Paschall/Frank Bunn, 1988 February 29 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 407 Barfield
  - File No.: 2206, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: D.U. Special Ventures Fund, 1988 June 29 (Box 24)
  - File No.: 2207, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: D.U. Special Ventures Fund, 1988 June 29 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Deyco
  - File No.: 2208, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sharon S. Poss, 1988 September 2 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Mangum Place, Durham, NC
  - File No.: 2209, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Janet E. Carpenter, 1987 November 30 (Box 24)
  - File No.: 2210, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John & Olga Attaway, 1985 June 26 (Box 24)
    County: Fulton, Comments/Location: Atlanta, Georgia
  - File No.: 2211, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sidney & Anne Allen, 1985 September 4 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Durham County, NC
  - File No.: 2212, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Investors Title Exchange Corp., 1989 February 13 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Carolantic Apartments
  - File No.: 2213, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. Thomas Hester, 1988 May 12 (Box 24)
    Comments/Location: Ralph R. Cooke Apartments
  - File No.: 2214, Grantee: Thomas & Magdalena Naylor, Grantor: Duke, 1994 December 19 (Box 24)
  - File No.: 2214, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas & Magdalena Naylor, 1994 December 15 (Box 24)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Duke Forest; .4 Acres
  - File No.: 2215, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Ottis & Clara Williams, 1977 April 1 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 309 Anderson St; Title Opinion
  - File No.: 2216, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Alton & Gladys Jones Bishop, 1994 December 29 (Box 24)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Orange County; Duke Forest
  - File No.: 2217, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas Hester, 1988 May 12 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Mangum Place - Harris Apartments
  - File No.: 2218, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Eunice & J. Leonard Goldner, 1995 September 15 (Box 24)
    County: Moore, Comments/Location: Pinehurst, NC
  - File No.: 2219, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Earl W. Mangum, 1988 March 25 (Box 24)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 409 Barfield Avenue
  - File No.: 2220, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Esther & John W. Hartman, 1986 November 17 (Box 25)
    Comments/Location: Lyme, CT
  - File No.: 2221, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Lawyers Title of N.C., 1989 August 9 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 2210-2212 Elba Street
  - File No.: 2222, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. Thomas Hester, 1988 May 12 (Box 25)
    Comments/Location: Leathers Property
  - File No.: 2223, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thompson Estate, 1989 November 13 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Rd.; Termination of Reversion Agrment.
  - File No.: 2224, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dr. John E. Dees, 1989 June 6 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: I-40 & Farrington Road - 1/2 interest
  - File No.: 2224, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dr. John E. Dees, 1992 December 23 (Box 25)
  - File No.: 2225, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Frances C. Brown, 1994 November 7 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1018 Rosehill Avenue - SOLD March 1995
  - File No.: 2225, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Frances C. Brown, 1994 November 7 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 2503 N. Duke Street - SOLD 10/3/95
  - File No.: 2225, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Frances C. Brown, 1994 November 7 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 2602 Nation Avenue - SOLD 10/3/95
  - File No.: 2225, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Frances C. Brown, 1994 November 7 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1306 Lakewood Avenue - SOLD 4/24/98
  - File No.: 2226, Grantee: Berndt & Angelika Mueller, Grantor: Berndt Mueller, 1995 November 17 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #8 and half of Lot #9, Comments/Location: 136 Pinecrest Road; file includes a map
  - File No.: 2227, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Gary Hock, 1996 April 18 (Box 25)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2021.
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Bonnie Brae
  - File No.: 2228, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: City of Durham, 1996 January 2 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Vincent Street closing
  - File No.: 2229, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Mary H. Dawson, Type: Deed, 1996 April 25 (Box 25)
    County: Carteret, Deed Book: 775, Page: 592, Map-Block-Lot: Block 203-Lot 2, Comments/Location: 2802 Evans Street., Morehead City
  - File No.: 2230, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Duke, Type: Title Opinion, 1991 May 15 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: DHN = PB 89, Pg 26, Comments/Location: Duke Hospital N & S & PG I & II
  - File No.: 2231, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wachovia Bank Executor/Estate Vada Couch Widener, Type: Deed, 1996 April 23 (Box 25)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 1457, Page: 323-328, Map-Block-Lot: Map 7.6..43, Comments/Location: note: +/-50 Ac, W/S and E/S Friends School Rd.
  - File No.: 2231, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wachovia Bank Executor/Estate Martha Couch Widener, Type: Deed, 1996 April 23 (Box 25)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 1457, Page: 329-335, Map-Block-Lot: Map 7.6..42, Comments/Location: note: +/-78 Ac, E/S Friends School Rd.
  - File No.: 2232, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Floyd C. Eubanks, Type: Deed, 1996 May 14 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1919 Yearby Ave., 305 & 307 Garden St.
  - File No.: 2233, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Jane Ann Lorch Nickerson, Type: Title Insur, 1996 April 15 (Box 25)
    County: Palm Beach, Conveyed by File No.: C-2234564, Deed Book: 39, Page: 44115, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #12, Comments/Location: First Addition Plat One Eagle's Nest
  - File No.: 2234, Grantee: Dale I. Vogel, Trustee, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1996 July 8 (Box 25)
    County: Orange, Map-Block-Lot: Eno TWP p.27, parcel 21A, Comments/Location: 35 acres of land/Hwy 10 near Landeau Drive
  - File No.: 2235, Grantee: Doris Mitchell, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1996 July 1 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 2211, Page: 125, Comments/Location: 921 Rome Ave. Durham; pd 2003 Cert Satisfaction
  - File No.: 2236, Grantee: Kathryne Brown, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1996 September 16 (Box 25)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: deed & pwr of atty for dot right of way
  - File No.: 2237, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dorothy Alexander Luchans, Type: War. Deed, 1996 July 17 (Box 25)
    County: Honolulu, Comments/Location: Condo on Ala Wai Blvd. in Honolulu, Hawaii
  - File No.: 2238, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Linwood & Ella Dean Grady, Type: Deed, 1974 May 14 (Box 25)